ingvysyabank.com 2015-03-18

# ING Vysya Bank - Personal Banking

At ING Vysya Bank Limited(IVBL), we recognize the importance of protecting the confidentiality and security of any personal information that we obtain from visitors of this web site. We are strongly committed to safeguarding your privacy online and have established the following privacy policy that will apply to you, as a visitor of the site:

  * You are not required to provide any personal information on this website unless you choose to do so. By submitting your personal information and pressing the 'submit' button, you consent to the content of this Privacy Policy and accept the conditions set out herein;
  * We do not sell or rent personal information.
  * Employees may not discuss the business affairs of any client with any other employee, except on a strict need-to-know basis.
  * We do not release client information, except upon a client's authorization or when permitted or required by law.
  * We will not sell your personal information to any third parties. We will only share the information with such third parties if and to the extent required by law or for regulatory purposes.
  * If the User has not attained 18 years of age, we do not encourage them to use the service or submit any personal information. Out of special concern for minor's privacy, IVBL does not accept personal information from persons who are stated to be under the age of 18.
  * This site may contain links to other sites. IVBL does not control the information collection of sites that can be reached through links from this or any site controlled by IVBL. If you have questions about the data collection procedures or privacy policy of linked sites, please contact those sites directly.
  * IVBL reserves the right to add, amend, revise, or suspend the privacy policy from time to time.
